// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
    options: [
      "Hyper Text Preprocessor",
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
      "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How Many Types Of Heading are there?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "5",
      "4",
      "2",
      "6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is the smallest heading?",
    answer: "h6",
    options: [
      "h1",
      "h4",
      "h6",
      "h2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which Tag is used for creating an ordered list?",
    answer: "ol",
    options: [
      "ul",
      "ol",
      "href",
      "b"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the extension of HTML?",
    answer: ".htm & .html",
    options: [
      ".html",
      ".htm",
      ".ht",
      ".htm & .html"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How is paragraph tag displayed in HTML?",
    answer: "p",
    options: [
      "pre",
      "p",
      "hr",
      "All the Above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Mark Tag is used for?",
    answer: "Highlighting text",
    options: [
      "Seo Ranking",
      "Highlighting text",
      "Filling color into text",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How to add image in Webpage?",
    answer: "img src",
    options: [
      "img src",
      "src image",
      "image",
      "img url"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How to add PDF in WebPage?",
    answer: "All of this",
    options: [
      "Iframe",
      "Object",
      "Embed",
      "All of this"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "SEO Tags are used for?",
    answer: "Ranking ",
    options: [
      "Ranking",
      "Commenting code",
      "CSS Property",
      "None of this"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];